http://lakhvinder.com/site/privacy-policy

Informatics III
Memory Prime (memory')
Log in
The PhilosophersThe Philosophers, by Gil Bruvel | www.Bruvel.com
The Forgotten GateThe Forgotten Gate, by Gil Bruvel | www.Bruvel.com
Dinosaurs, Giants of PatagoniaA still from Dinosaurs, Giants of Patagonia. Studio Virtuel Concept and it's clients.
Lakhvinder hp EliteBook 8730w field & lab instrument in ivyLakhvinder hp EliteBook 8730w field & lab instrument in ivy during Lakhvinder|TS experiments. Photograph by Lakhvinder Singh Takhar.
Lakhvinder hp EliteBook 8730w field & lab instrument in a treeLakhvinder hp EliteBook 8730w field & lab instrument in a tree during Lakhvinder|TS experiments. Photograph by Lakhvinder Singh Takhar.
Carousel Featured ShowlistThe PhilosophersThe Philosophers, by Gil Bruvel | www.Bruvel.comThe Forgotten GateThe Forgotten Gate, by Gil Bruvel | www.Bruvel.comDinosaurs, Giants of PatagoniaA still from Dinosaurs, Giants of Patagonia. Studio Virtuel Concept and it's clients.Lakhvinder hp EliteBook 8730w field & lab instrument in ivyLakhvinder hp EliteBook 8730w field & lab instrument in ivy during Lakhvinder|TS experiments. Photograph by Lakhvinder Singh Takhar.Lakhvinder hp EliteBook 8730w field & lab instrument in a treeLakhvinder hp EliteBook 8730w field & lab instrument in a tree during Lakhvinder|TS experiments. Photograph by Lakhvinder Singh Takhar.
HomeSitePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Details
Written by Lakhvinder Singh Takhar
Category: Site
Created: 12 March 2009
Privacy Policy
This Web site does not collect personally identifiable information.
The Registration form integrates the information you provide into a Lakhvinder internal CRM system in such a manner that the information is not stored by this Web site. Said information is used only for internal operations and is not released to third parties except as set forth below.
This Web site does utilize cookies.
This Web site does collect standard security and diagnostics logging information such as;
your IP address.
a log of your use, and time of use, associated with your IP address.
standard information about your browser, machine and operating system which is freely disclosed by your browser.
Some information may be derived from the aforementioned information for purposes such as statistical analysis of behavior by;
geographical region.
domain.
browser.
operating system.
Said derived information is not used to derive your personal identity nor any personally identifiable information other than that which may be incidentally derived such as a personal domain or a browser which openly broadcasts your name, user name or other information.
Information may be used to derive your identity and personally identifiable information about you, and, said information may be released to appropriate authorities;
if you access this Web site in a malicious manner.
in response to a legal or governmental order.
Registration and account creation are subject to additional terms which are presented at the time of said account creation.
Trending Articles
Lakhvinder Singh Takhar
Bakhsho Kaur Takhar
Company Overview
Lakhvinder | TS ™: Secure and robust IoT, mass scale autonomous control and predictive analytics for defense, intelligence, transportation and industrial applications. 2007-2012
Dinosaurs, Giants of Patagonia. 2007
The Elf King. 2000-2001
Star Trek ®: Secret of Vulcan Fury. 1997-1999
Of Light & Darkness: The Prophecy. 1997-1999
Star Trek ®: Starfleet Academy. 1997-1999
Hewlett-Packard ®
Toyota Land Cruiser Advertisement. 1998
Software based model and simulator of BFM ™ SAViM ™ IV hardware. 2008
The modeling and simulation of amorphous state and ordered crystalline state phase change of Ge-Sb-Te alloys using hnc: heavy node computing. 2008
Most Favoured Books, by requested categories
The Adaptation of ZigBee for Military and Intelligence Applications in Ambient Intelligence. 2007
New Articles
Bakhsho Kaur Takhar
Engagement Mentions
Jas Takhar
TS fully integrated final development wrap-up and testing series. 2010-2012
An analysis of flocking behaviour in MotoGP motorcycle racing. 2010
Trending Downloads
Hewlett-Packard
Territorial Saturation (Restricted)
Draft v1.4 (26 pages)
Formal v2.0 (350 pages)
Current v6.0 (2,498 pages)
Project Firepower
Dessinn's Serafin
Panasonic Toughbook
Menu
Home
About
Portfolio
Alliances & Instruments
Site
Access or Use of this Web site constitutes Your Acceptance of, and Agreement to, the Terms of Use.
© Copyright 1982-2015 Lakhvinder David Takhar center for advanced studies. All rights reserved. Some Resources are © Copyright Lakhvinder's licensors, suppliers and/or other third parties. All rights reserved.
Go to top
